Sometimes you got to leave a place and
you really don't want to go. I like the
out of this little private beach.
That's what Colombia's been like for me.
>> The view from my homie Sebastian's
house.
>> I got to do amazing things here like
meet my first indigenous tribe. This is
the village of the Kogi. Dive in crystal
blue water and spear a fish.
>> Just got out of the water. I shot two
fish.
>> out with subsistence fishermen who fish
every day to eat.
>> how we fish in right now in Colombia.
>> I walked barefoot through a jungle.
[music]
I got to see horses riding on the beach.
>> Today I'm going to come back here and
I'm going to ride a horse. Beautiful
mountain vistas. Most people only
experience [music] it from down there.
>> I met a new friend named Sebastian.
>> The pattern on the housing. I ate good
food, fried tilapia, some coconut rice,
some fried plantains, heard good music.
People out everywhere. There's music
playing.
>> I bought an 80 cent [music] beer. 80
cent beer. I you not. I just paid
80 cents for a beer.
>> The lost city is here, Ciudad Perdida.
>> How epic is that?
>> I talked [music] to one guy who said he
knows over 50 unknown archaeological
sites. There are real natives living in
the forest traditionally with ancient
wisdom that I have to come back and get.
>> I don't know when I'm going to be back,
but I'm going to bring a group with me.
Hell, I don't want to leave now. But I
miss my woman Alex and the ship hopping
in Costa Rica. Joe is signing out from
the beautiful Colors Hostel. Check the
view.